arcadeweb.com 2014-06-27

# Free Tournament Games by Arcadeweb

| 

ARCADEWEB PRIVACY POLICY

ArcadeWeb makes this website, [www.arcadeweb.com](http://www.arcadeweb.com/) (the "Site"), available to users of the Site and registered members of the Site (collectively, "Users", and also referred herein as "you"), subject to this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") and the ArcadeWeb Terms of Use ("Terms of Use"). This Policy explains what information ArcadeWeb LLC (referred to herein as "ArcadeWeb", "Company", "we", “us”, or “our”) collects from Users who visit the Site and/or participate in the resources offered by ArcadeWeb. This Policy also explains how the Company uses and maintains that information.

ArcadeWeb has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe Privacy Seal covers only information that is collected through this Site. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). **  
**

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the Site’s home page prior to the change becoming effective.

This Policy applies only to information collected through the Site and Software (as defined below), but not to information collected or obtained from other sources.

We collect two kinds of information through the Site. The first kind is information that can identify you as a specific individual - such as your name and email address (“Personally Identifiable Information” or "PII"). We only collect PII when you register to set up an account, contact us directly or forward content from the Site to someone else, such as when you use our "Send Game to Friend" feature. (See "Collection of Personally Identifiable Information" below). The second kind of information is the kind of non-personally identifiable information ("NPII") collected and stored automatically by many websites. It includes, for example, information about your Internet service provider, operating system, type of browser, geographic location, and pages viewed on the Site. Although this information is related to you, it is not associated with your PII and cannot be linked to you personally. If you register to play the games on the Site, the NPII collected may also include your IP address and HTML information about the content of web pages you visit.

If you do not want your information to continue to be collected and used as provided in this Policy, you should not access or use the Site again.

ArcadeWeb offers games on the Site free of charge in exchange for the Users’ agreement to install the ArcadeWeb software (the "Software") on their computers or other computing device. The Software allows us to display text link, transitional and banner advertisements based on the web content viewed by that User. No PII is collected through the Software. In addition, the Site and games on the Site may display advertisements from third parties before and/or during gameplay. All advertisements from the Software, Site and games on the Site shall collectively be known as “Third Party Content”.

Your dealings with Third Party Content, including, but not limited to, your interaction with its advertisements and promotions, purchase of its goods, or any other type of involvement, are solely between you and the third party. Therefore we do not endorse the advertisements, products or other materials of the Third Party Content. If you interact with the Third Party Content, their terms and conditions and privacy policies apply to your rights and obligations with respect to such interaction. Accordingly, such third parties may collect personal or non-personal information about you. **  
**

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

PII is collected by ArcadeWeb only when you provide it to us by using one of the following Site features:

  * In order to use the Site, you must register to set up an account, providing your email address and creating a user name (an alias that will be your player name) and a password. You also need to provide a photo (or elect to use the default photo provided by the Site) and create a user profile. The profile you create on the Site will be publically accessible unless otherwise indicated. ArcadeWeb works with other companies to offer its content and services to users of their Web sites ("Partner Site(s)"). Even if you enter ArcadeWeb from a Partner Site, you will need to register through ArcadeWeb, and, therefore, this Policy applies to ArcadeWeb's collection of your PII.
  * In order to have prizes awarded to your ArcadeWeb account, you need to provide your first and last name, email address, contact phone number and mailing address so that you can be notified and make arrangements for delivery of your prize. You also are required, in order to collect a prize, to provide your age, date of birth, a photo and a photo id that matches your photo and address, so that ArcadeWeb can verify your identity and maintain the integrity of its operations. You are also requested, but not required, to provide additional demographic information, such as your geographic location, gender and ethnicity, for inclusion on the ArcadeWeb "Winners' Page."
  * When you notify us of a problem with the operation of the Site or submit a suggestion, complaint, question, request, or any other email correspondence, ArcadeWeb asks for your email address or phone number so that you can receive a response. This information will only be used to notify you of receipt of your submission and of a resolution to the inquiry.
  * By registering for an account, you agree that ArcadeWeb may display your player name and competition results. You also give us the right to use your name and likeness in any publicity regarding prizes that you win, regardless of the cash amount or value of the prize.
  * If you are a US taxpayer and your total winnings on ArcadeWeb in any given calendar year reach a total of $600, ArcadeWeb will request that you submit your social security number in order to send you a Form 1099, as required by Internal Revenue Service regulations. Failure to provide your social security number at that time will prevent you from participating in game tournaments.
  * If you choose to invite a friend to join ArcadeWeb through our Tell A Friend feature, we will ask you for your friend's email address so that you can send a personal message inviting him or her to visit the Site. Your friend's email address will only be used to send that one message and it will not be stored or otherwise used. **  
**

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

The Site may include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

If you do not want us to collect your PII as described above or to use and share your PII as described further below in this Policy, you should NOT provide it to us through any of the Site features described above. By providing us with your PII using any of these features, you are authorizing our use and sharing of your PII as described in this Policy and any subsequent revisions to this Policy that we may publish on the Site. **  
**

**Single Sign-On**

You can log in to the Site using the Facebook Connect sign-in service. This service will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  The Facebook Connect sign-in service gives you the option to post information about your activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your network. **  
**

**Updating Your Personally Identifiable Information**

If your PII changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or remove it by emailing our Customer Support at [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. **  
**

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years of age. We cannot and will not independently verify that all of our Users are at least 13 years old, but we will remove from our files any PII of anyone we discover to be under 13 years old. **  
**

**Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

We reserve the right to use PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (2) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; and (3) as otherwise stated in this Policy.

We do not share, sell or trade any of your PII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your PII with our parent company and its principals, employees, consultants, officers, directors, members, agents, subsidiaries, or affiliates (collectively "Related Companies"). Neither we nor our Related Companies contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your PII.

We and our Related Companies may provide access to your PII when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of other users or the public.

We and/or our Related Companies may also disclose your PII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Companies may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist in distributing e-mails; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; (g) manage our sweepstakes and contests; and/or (h) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site. We and our Related Companies require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we or our Related Companies go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the ArcadeWeb home page of any such change in ownership or control of your PII. We also reserve the right to disclose PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. **  
**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

As with many websites, when you visit the Site, it automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical and statistical information is used to customize your experience at the Site, to help us improve the quality of the Site and to make your visits easy, convenient and fun. ArcadeWeb also collects your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Site server and for Site administration purposes.

In addition to the general collection of NPII by the Site (including, but not limited to, IP address, browser type, operating system version, time and date stamp, and landing page), the Software collects your IP addresses, browser information, URLs, HTML, web pages and/or search queries on the web pages you visit. We may use this NPII to assist us in delivering to you more relevant content in the form of Third Party Content, which appears when you are online generally. We may also work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver such Third Party Content to you. We may share your NPII and/or aggregated information with our third party partners to improve the relevancy of such Third Party Content. These third party partners, including, but not limited to, advertising networks and advertisers, may also use cookies and other technologies to collect and track NPII such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering Third Party Content that is more relevant to your interests. They may also utilize supplemental data from other sources and analytics methods to help deliver more relevant Third Party Content. A Premium User may have the option to opt-out of receiving certain Third Party Content. To opt out of certain Third Party Content, click the applicable link contained in the placement of such Third Party Content and follow the disabling instructions. When you opt-out, the Software will place a cookie in your browser so that you will stop receiving that particular Third Party Content. If you delete or refresh cookies, that certain Third Party Content will be automatically re-activated. In addition, you may continue to have access to Premium Games and to receive other Third Party Content after opting out. However, if at any time, a Premium User no longer wants the Software or to receive any Third Party Content, s/he may uninstall the Software and its associated monitoring technologies (including its collection of NPII). The directions for uninstalling the Software are set forth below in the section entitled "Uninstall Software."

You can opt out of the use of your NPII from being used by Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) members. The NAI opt-out tool was developed in conjunction with NAI members for the express purpose of allowing consumers to "opt out" of the behavioral advertising delivered by NAI members. If you opt-out of the use of your NPII from being used by NAI members, you will continue to receive ads, however, it will prevent NAI members from delivering ads tailored to your preferences and usage patterns. If you opt out of Interest-Based Advertising (as defined [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/what-is-it)) by one or more NAI member company, that choice will be stored in “opt-out cookies.” If you ever delete opt-out cookies from your browser (such as by clearing all cookies), buy a new computer, or change web browsers, you'll need to renew your opt-out choices. NAI member companies need to be able to read an "opt-out" cookie on your browser to know not to collect and use data for interest-based advertising purposes. For more information or to opt-out click <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. **  
**

**Cookies**

The Site uses "cookies" and similar means to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and to enhance your experience at the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The Site uses cookies to recognize your preferences, temporarily store session information (such as your login to a download or support area), and to remember you when you register for our products and/or services. This helps save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your customized content and advertising on your later visits to the Site. It also allows you to move from page to page at the Site without having to sign in again on each page. Please note, if you opt-out of certain Third Party Content (as explained earlier), the Software will place a cookie in your browser so that you will stop receiving that particular Third Party Content. If you delete or refresh cookies, that certain Third Party Content will be automatically re-activated. You can follow the instructions again to opt-out of certain Third Party Content. If you do not want the Site to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site and it may affect your ability to use some of the products and/or services at the Site. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set. **  
**

**Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our third party advertisers as well as third party ad servers is not covered by our privacy policy (as explained in the NPII section above). We do not have access or control over these cookies. These third parties use session ID cookies to gather anonymous information. **  
**

**Flash LSOs**

Third parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on the Site or to display Third Party Content to you, use LSOs to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

**Web Beacons**

The Site may contain electronic images known as "web beacons" which are also sometimes called single-pixel gifs. Web beacons may be used to assist in delivering cookies, allow us to count Users who have visited the Site pages and to deliver services via the Site. We may also include web beacons in email messages or newsletters you agree to receive in order to determine whether such messages have been opened and acted upon. If any partner advertises on the Site, we may work with them to place web beacons on their website to allow ArcadeWeb to collect statistics on how often clicking on those advertisements on the Site results in a purchase or other action on such partner's website. ArcadeWeb may also employ web beacons from third party partners in order to help compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of the Site. ArcadeWeb will never allow web beacons on the Site to be used by third parties (other than Related Companies) to collect or access your personal information. We do not tie web beacons to any PII you submit while on our Site. **  
**

**Use and Sharing of Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII)**

We do not share, sell or trade any of your NPII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your NPII with our Related Companies. Neither we nor our Related Companies contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your NPII.

We and our Related Companies may provide access to your NPII to third parties when legally required to do so, to allow third party advertising networks to serve you more relevant ads as described above, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site and/or to limit our legal liability and protect our rights.

We and/or our Related Companies may also disclose your NPII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Companies may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist in distributing e-mails; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; (g) manage our sweepstakes and contests; and/or (h) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site. We and our Related Companies require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we or our Related Companies go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your NPII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the ArcadeWeb home page of any such change in ownership or control of your NPII. We also reserve the right to disclose NPII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. **  
**

**Security**

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect Information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to our authorized employees and personnel of the Related Companies. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any information transmitted to us or through the Site will be at your own risk. **  
**

**Opt-Out of ArcadeWeb Emails**

If you are receiving emails from ArcadeWeb, it is because we understood from your participation on our Site that you were interested in receiving ongoing information from us. If at any point you no longer want to receive emails from ArcadeWeb, you may at any time go [here](http://www.arcadeweb.com/deactivate.php) and follow the 'opt out' directions there. If you have any questions about the opt-out process, you can contact us at [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com). Also, please note that if we have already shared your information with one of our business partners, unsubscribing from our list will not prevent these third parties from emailing you. You will have to send an opt-out request to those third parties directly. Opportunities to "opt out" from receiving emails are usually found on these companies' websites or within each of their email communications. **  
**

**Links from the Site**

The Site provides links to the websites of many third parties. If you click through to any of these third party web sites, our Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those third party sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including but not limited to their privacy policies. We shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. All inquiries concerning the use of PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party and not to ArcadeWeb. **  
**

**Uninstall Software**

Users who have downloaded the Software and who do not want their NPII collected as described above should immediately uninstall the Software. You may uninstall the Software by going [here](http://www.arcadeweb.com/deactivate.php) and following the directions to remove the Software from your computer, or by selecting the appropriate entry in your Control Panel using the "Add or Remove Programs" icon. Uninstalling the Software means that you will no longer have access to the games on the Site. **  
**

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request by email to [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com). Please allow 30 days for a response. **  
**

**QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Policy or its implementation, please email us at [privacy@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:privacy@ArcadeWeb.com). For general questions about ArcadeWeb, please email us at [support@ArcadeWeb.com](mailto:support@ArcadeWeb.com). Alternatively, you may call our Customer Service number, 1-877-406-4693 or write to us at ArcadeWeb, 3419 Via Lido #261, Newport Beach, CA 92663, Attn: Legal Department.

Effective: April 28, 2009

Last Updated: February 11, 2014

|
